{
  "subtestId": 92,
  "subtestGUID": "b9f7b132b974c1b4e040a8c0420116a9",
  "title": "Word Reasoning",
  "displayName": "Word Reasoning",
  "abbr": "Word Reasoning",
  "testType": "wais",
  "testTitle": "WISC-IV",
  "testDisplayName": "WISC-IV",
  "normType": "wisc-iv",
  "testGUID": "bd451bc0ee253d9be040a8c0420111e3",
  "subtestType": null,
  "language": "en",
  "shouldDefaultRecordAudio": true,
  "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning",
  "isWritingRequired": true,
  "skipSubsequentTrialsRule": false,
  "scaledScorePerItem": false,
  "isTimeRemainMsgRequired": false,
  "unscoredResponseRule": false,
  "designCopyingScoreSwitchingRule": false,
  "metaData": {
    "rules": 
    [
      {
        "type": "age",
        "minAge": {
          "year": 6,
          "month": 0
        },
        "maxAge": {
          "year": 16,
          "month": 11
        }
      }
    ],
    "subtestCategory": "Verbal Comprehension",
    "averageDuration": 10,
    "descriptionCS": "The child identifies the common concept being described in a series of clues."
  },
  "scoringScaleName": "Verbal Comprehension Index (VCI)",
  "scoringScaleAbbr": "VCI",
  "isScaledScoreOptional": true,
  "questions": 
  [
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-dog",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-dog",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Sample Item A",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Sample",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-dog/wisciv-wordreasoning-dogPrompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": true,
              "question": "<p><strong><span class=\"speechBlue\">This is an animal that goes &ldquo;woof.&rdquo; What is it?<\u002fspan><\u002fstrong><\u002fp>\r\n\r\n<p>Allow approximately 5 seconds for a response.<\u002fp>\r\n",
              "correct": "<p>[Dog]: Say, <span class=\"speechBlue\"><strong>Right. A dog is an animal that goes &ldquo;woof.&rdquo; Let&rsquo;s try another one.<\u002fstrong><\u002fspan><\u002fp>\r\n",
              "wrong": "<p>Say, <strong><span class=\"speechBlue\">It is a dog. A dog is an animal that goes &ldquo;woof.&rdquo; Let&rsquo;s try another one.<\u002fspan><\u002fstrong><\u002fp>\r\n"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "html",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice"
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
        {
          "name": ">5 seconds",
          "guid": "2e702a3efce144fd907ccf3926242e63",
          "abbreviation": "mf",
          "isPopover": true
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-mop",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-mop",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Sample Item B",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Sample",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-mop/wisciv-wordreasoning-mopPrompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "<p>\r\n\t<span class=\"speechBlue\">This has a long handle...What is it?<\u002fspan><\u002fp>\r\n<p>\r\n\t<span class=\"pointGray\">Allow approximately 5 seconds for a response.<\u002fspan><\u002fp>\r\n",
              "correct": "<p>\r\n\t<span class=\"pointGray\">[Mop]: Say,&nbsp;<\u002fspan><span class=\"speechBlue\">Right. A mop has a long handle. Let&#39;s try another one.<\u002fspan><\u002fp>\r\n",
              "wrong": "<p>\r\n\t<span class=\"pointGray\">Present the second clue.<\u002fspan><\u002fp>\r\n"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "<p>\r\n\t<span class=\"speechBlue\">This has a long handle, and is used with water to clean the floor. What is it?<\u002fspan><\u002fp>\r\n<p>\r\n\t<span class=\"pointGray\">Allow approximately 5 seconds for a response.<\u002fspan><\u002fp>\r\n",
              "correct": "<p>\r\n\t<span class=\"pointGray\">[Mop]: Say,&nbsp;<\u002fspan><span class=\"speechBlue\">Right. A mop has a long handle, and is used with water to clean the floor. Let&#39;s try another one.<\u002fspan><\u002fp>\r\n",
              "wrong": "<p>\r\n\t<span class=\"pointGray\">Say,<span class=\"speechBlue\">&nbsp;<\u002fspan><\u002fspan><span class=\"speechBlue\">It is a mop. A mop has a long handle, and is used with water to clean the floor.&nbsp;Let&#39;s try another one.<\u002fspan><\u002fp>\r\n"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "html",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice"
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
        {
          "name": ">5 seconds",
          "guid": "da8f06d9841642568db398897fec57e1",
          "abbreviation": "mf",
          "isPopover": true
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item1",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item1",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 1",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This is used to dry yourself after a bath.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Towel; Hair-dryer; Blow-dryer; Rag; Cloth",
            "incorrect": "Bathtub; Bathroom"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item2",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item2",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 2",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This has a knob and people can open it and walk through it.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Door; Screen door [Any specific door]; Gate",
            "incorrect": "Door (knob, handle); Cabinet"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item3",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item3",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 3",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This is the part of your head used to smell things.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Nose; Nostril",
            "incorrect": "Face; Mind; Brain; Sense; Mouth; Tongue"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item4",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item4",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 4",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This is an animal with a long trunk and big ears.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Elephant",
            "incorrect": "Deer; Aardvark; Anteater"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item5",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item5",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 5",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This is something you wear to cover your head.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Hat; Baseball hat [Any specific hat]; Hood; Cap; Helmet; Scarf; Wig; Hair; Bandana; Mask",
            "incorrect": "Blanket; Towel"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item6",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item6",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 6",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This is a room where people sleep.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Bedroom; Guest Room",
            "incorrect": "Bed; Apartment; Hotel"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item7",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item7",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 7",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This is on the ground after it rains...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it can make your clothes dirty.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Mud; Wet (grass, dirt); Puddles; Dirty water; Snow; Slush; Ice",
            "incorrect": "Frost; Moisture; Grass; Water; Dirt; Clay"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item8",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item8",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 8",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This comes in many colors...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it is used on walls.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Paint; Wallpaper; Picture; Frame; Poster; Curtains; Fabric; Painting; Chalk",
            "incorrect": "Rainbow; Fall leaves; Crayons; Markers; Pen"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item9",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item9",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 9",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This is a place of learning...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it can have many things from the past in it.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "School; College; University; Classroom; Class; Museum; Library; Church",
            "incorrect": "Laboratory; Book; Memory; Daycare; Home"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item10",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item10",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 10",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This is up in the sky...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and you can only see these at night.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Stars; Northern Lights; Aurora borealis; Constellations; Planets; Satellite; Firefly",
            "incorrect": "Sun; Moon; Clouds; Bats; Owls; Airplanes"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item11",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item11",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 11",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This is what people do to make things \"like new\"...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and people do this to things that are broken.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Repair; Fix; Rebuild; Reassemble; Refurbish; Renovate; Restore; Put back together; Mend; Reconstruct; Repaint; Refurnish; Refinish ",
            "incorrect": "Redo; Renew; Build; Upgrade; Clean; Refresh; Take it to the shop; Glue; Tape"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item12",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item12",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 12",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This can make food taste better...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it can be found in the ocean.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Salt",
            "incorrect": "Water; Seaweed; Seasonings"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item13",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item13",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 13",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This is found in nature...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it has water flowing from its mouth.",
              "correct": "Correct ",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "River; Stream; Creek; Brook; Spring; Waterfall; Fountain; Harbor; Bay; Inlet",
            "incorrect": "Ocean; Sea; Whale; Rain; Well; Canal"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item14",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item14",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 14",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "These are protected by skin and bones...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and they can sometimes be replaced.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Organ; Heart; [Any organ that can be replaced]; Tissue; Blood; Plasma; Nerves; Muscle; Arteries; Veins; Bone marrow [Any tissue that can be replaced]; Cartilage",
            "incorrect": "Skin; Tonsils; Brain; Teeth; Bones; Operation; Body parts; Insides; Cell"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item15",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item15",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 15",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This can be broken...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it is written down to protect people.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Law; Rule; Contract; Policy; Will; Constitution; Declaration of Independence [Any specific historic document]; Treaty; Amendment; Agreement; Rights",
            "incorrect": "Pledge; Insurance; Instructions"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item16",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item16",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 16",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This leads to new discoveries...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it involves a step-by-step process...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it may include experiments.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Science; Research; Scientific method; Inventing; Invention; Investigation; Biology [Any specific science]; Problem solving; Experimentation; Deductive reasoning; Hypothesis; Exploration; Technology; Theories",
            "incorrect": "Lab tests; Testing; Projects; Microscopes; Learning; Teaching; Study"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item17",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item17",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 17",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This allows people to do or own something...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it is given by the government...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and people may have to take a test to get it.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Visa; License; Driver's license [Any specific license]; Permit; Green card; Citizenship; Scholarship; Grant; Naturalization; Patent; Copyright; Diploma; Degree",
            "incorrect": "Welfare; Food stamps; Right to vote; Land grant; Job; Work; Grade"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item18",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item18",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 18",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This is something most people want...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and conflict prevents it...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and governments try to keep it.",
              "correct": "Correct ",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Peace; Freedom; Liberty; Law; Security; Control; Power; Order; Justice; Rights; Rules; Money; Wealth; Safety; Authority",
            "incorrect": "Revolution; Ownership of land; Leadership; State; Country"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item19",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item19",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 19",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This is something everything has...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it changes every year...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it can never decrease.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Age; Birthday; Height",
            "incorrect": "Calendar; Years; Months; Weight; Size; Time; Growth; Skin; Weather; Temperature; Air"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item20",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item20",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 20",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This can't be touched ...",
              "correct": "Correct ",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it can't go backward ...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it can't stop.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Time; Aging; Gravity; Earth's rotation; Light",
            "incorrect": "Age; Wind; History; Future; Air; Year [Any specific unit of time]"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item21",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item21",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 21",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This is a place...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it is protected from the weather...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it is found within something else.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Inside; Room; Bedroom [Any specific room]; Basement; Storm cellar; Attic; Indoors; Vault; Safe; Shelter; (Underground, Bomb, Fallout) shelter; Cave; Tunnel; Bunker",
            "incorrect": "House; [Any specific building]; Underground; Harbor; Cove; Apartment; Store in a mall"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item22",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item22",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 22",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This can be a river...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and wars can change it...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and two countries can share it.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Boundary; Border; Border line; Territory (marker, line); Canal; Rio Grande [Any specific river border]",
            "incorrect": "Dam; Bridge; Divide; Landmark; Wall; Nile [Any specific non-border river]; Split between"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item23",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item23",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 23",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This is made by people...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it can not be touched...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it has already happened.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "History; Past; Past (actions, thoughts, decisions, mistakes); Yesterday; Memories; Discoveries",
            "incorrect": "News story; Future; War; Millennium; [Any historical event]; Baby; Birth"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item24",
      "shouldUseTimer": false,
      "forceReloadBefore": false,
      "baseUrl": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/wisciv-wordreasoning-item24",
      "subtestName": "Word Reasoning",
      "usesStims": false,
      "shouldShowStimTouches": false,
      "isWritingRequired": true,
      "title": "Item 24",
      "nameElements": 
      [
      ],
      "questionType": "Score",
      "isTeachingItem": false,
      "useTimedSwitch": false,
      "isShowInstruction": false,
      "useDashboard": false,
      "hideStimWhenLeavingItem": false,
      "promptBlocks": 
      [
        {
          "minAge": null,
          "maxAge": null,
          "filepath": "battery/wisc-iv/word_reasoning/items_1-24Prompts.html"
        }
      ],
      "suppressInstructionCard": false,
      "predefinedBehavior": {
        "data": {
          "choiceList": 
          [
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "This has never been seen or done before...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it can make our lives better or easier...",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            },
            {
              "disableTextHighlight": false,
              "shouldShowIncorrectItemsFirst": false,
              "disableBlueFont": false,
              "question": "and it is a product of the mind.",
              "correct": "Correct",
              "wrong": "Incorrect"
            }
          ],
          "isClueTypeQuestion": true,
          "dataType": "text",
          "behaviorName": "forcedChoice",
          "sampleAnswers": {
            "correct": "Discovery; Invention; Innovation; Technology; Imagination; Creativity; Dream",
            "incorrect": "Hope; Happiness; Intergalactic travel [Any discovery that has not happened]; Thoughts; Learning; Peace; Idea; Telepathy; Information"
          }
        },
        "superType": null,
        "type": "forcedRecognition"
      },
      "contextualEventBtn": 
      [
      ]
    }
  ],
  "consecutiveZerosDiscontinueRule": {
    "type": "consecutiveZerosDiscontinueRule",
    "value": 5,
    "description": "This subtest discontinues after 5 consecutive scores of 0 points.",
    "countsDemoItems": false
  },
  "reverseRule": 
  [
    {
      "minAge": 10,
      "maxAge": 16,
      "skipFromQuestionID": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item1",
      "skipToQuestionID": "wisciv-wordreasoning-item5",
      "reverseWithForwardSequence": false,
      "noSkipMsg": "If suspected of intellectual deficiency",
      "numberFullScores": 2
    }
  ],
  "contextualEvents": 
  [
    {
      "name": "DK",
      "guid": "54fccacc43864aaea854f9f9b70145c5",
      "abbreviation": "DK"
    },
    {
      "name": "NR",
      "guid": "80b62087aca14dfd807069b86307f358",
      "abbreviation": "NR"
    },
    {
      "name": "R",
      "guid": "c973a426598d48b3a5a2395535685c1c",
      "abbreviation": "R"
    }
  ],
  "shouldShowStartPoints": null
}